

### YESHI TSERING GANGCHEN

## web and mobile developer

Looking for a 4-month minimum internship

#### **Contact**

- 06 95 91 19 37
- yestsering@gmail.com

in gangchen-yeshi-tsering

10 Rue de la Mégisserie, 92220 Bagneux

### **Qualities**

- Motivated and dynamic
- Pedagogue
- Patient and hardworking
- Punctual and careful

### Skills

- HTML/CSS
- BootStrap
- JQuery
- JavaScript
- React JS
- React Native
- MongoDB
- Node JS
- SQL

### Software and hardware

- Git
- Adobe Photoshop
- Ms Office
- In Design
- Hardware

#### Languages

French: Beginner

English: Intermediate

Tibetan: Native language

During seven years working in information technologies, I learned and discovered a passion for computer sciences. My fascination for web development and mobile technologies drove me to intensive learning of these skills through specific certifications. I'm currently following a specialized degree on web & mobile development with Konexio in order to become an expert as a full stack web & mobile developer. I'm therefore looking for a 4 to 6 months internship, I am available now.

### **Projects**

- https://github.com/gangchenyeshi
- https://gangchenyeshi.github.io

### **Professional experiences**

#### IT teacher, Tibet | 2010-17

- Computer instructor in school, using Microsoft Office tools
- Creating and design school magazine.
- Installation of Windows operating systems and application software
- Computer troubleshooting and networking

#### Team member, Prêt à Manger Paris | 2019-20

- Work as a key team member in a restaurant.
- Customer welcome and service
- Monitor the preservation of perishable products and remove products unfit for cooking
- Storage and cleaning of the point of sale

### **Degrees & certifications**

#### Computer training (Digitous), Konexio, Paris | 2020-21

• Web and Mobile Developer

#### Bachelor degree, Tibet | 2004

Computer science

#### Diploma advanced language french, Lyon | 2019

■ Level A2

#### **Personal Information**

Name : Yeshi Tsering GANGCHEN

Age : 39 yrs Marital status : Married



### YESHI TSERING GANGCHEN

## Développeur Web et mobile

Cherche un stage de 4 mois minimum

### **Contact**

06 95 91 19 37

yestsering@gmail.comgangchen-yeshi-tsering

10 Rue de la Mégisserie, 92220 Bagneux

### Qualités

- Motivé et dynamique
- Pédagogue
- Patient et travailleur
- Ponctuel et attentif

### Compétences

- HTML/CSS
- BootStrap
- JQuery
- JavaScript
- React JS
- React Native
- MongoDB
- Node JS
- SQL

# \*\*\*

### Logiciel et matériel

- Git
- Adobe Photoshop
- Ms Office
- In Design
- Matériel informatique

### Langues

Français : Débutant

Anglais : Intermédiaire

Tibétain : Maternelle

Pendant sept ans de travail dans les technologies de l'information, j'ai appris et découvert une passion pour l'informatique. Ma fascination pour le développement Web et les technologies mobiles m'a poussé à m'orienter et à acquérir ces compétences grâce à des certifications de développement spécialisées. Je suis actuellement en formation de développeur web & mobile avec Konexio à Paris pour devenir un expert développeur web & mobile full stack. Dans ce cadre, je suis à la recherche d'un stage de 4 à 6 mois, je suis disponible dés maintenant

### **Projets**

- https://github.com/gangchenyeshi
- https://gangchenyeshi.github.io

### **Expériences professionnelles**

#### **Enseignant Informatique, Tibet | 2010-17**

- Enseignement informatique au collège, sur les outils Microsoft Office
- Design et conception graphique
- Installation de systèmes d'exploitation Windows
- Dépannage informatique

#### Member de l'équipe, Prêt à Manger Paris | 2019-20

- Travaillent en équipe dans un restaurant.
- Accueil et service du client
- Surveillance la conservation des produits périssables et enlève les produits impropres à la cuisine
- Rangement et nettoyage du point de vente

### **Diplômes**

Formation informatique (Digitous), Konexio, Paris | 2020-21

• Développeur Web et Mobile

Lycée Bac + 3, Tibet | 2004

Informatique

Diplôme Approfondi de Langue Française, Lyon | 2019

Niveau A2

### Informations personnelles

Nom & Prénom: Yeshi Tsering GANGCHEN

Âge : 39 ans Status martial : marié